<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<changelogs>
    <changelog>
        <element>com_alfa</element>
        <type>component</type>
        <version>1.2.0</version>

        <change>
            <item>Standardised every bundled plugin namespace to the Alfa\ vendor prefix (alfa-shipments and alfa-payments Standard, and the alfa-fields plugins). Internal refactor only — no schema change and no effect on stored data.</item>
        </change>
    </changelog>
    <changelog>
        <element>com_alfa</element>
        <type>component</type>
        <version>1.1.0</version>

        <change>
            <item>Ship the GPL-3 LICENSE file with the package — installed into the component directory and covered by the file-integrity check.</item>
        </change>
    </changelog>
    <changelog>
        <element>com_alfa</element>
        <type>component</type>
        <version>1.0.11</version>

        <fix>
            <item>Fixed bundled module and plugin names appearing as raw language keys (e.g. MOD_ALFA_SEARCH_NAME, PLG_SYSTEM_ALFASYNC_XML_NAME) in the User Actions Log and Extensions manager. Manifest names now match each extension's element so Joomla resolves them to their human-readable titles.</item>
        </fix>
    </changelog>
    <changelog>
        <element>com_alfa</element>
        <type>component</type>
        <version>1.0.10</version>

        <fix>
            <item>Fixed a latent infinite recursion in the plugin layout event setter (onSetLayoutData), which could overflow the stack when layout data was supplied through the event's magic setter.</item>
        </fix>

        <change>
            <item>Internal housekeeping: removed stray developer backup files that were inadvertently included in the package.</item>
            <item>Refined the payment/shipment plugin event model so redirect and inline template rendering are available only where they apply — the checkout views and the gateway-return step; order place/save hooks are now strictly data hooks.</item>
            <item>Expanded developer documentation in the bundled Standard payment plugin — the gateway-return (onPaymentResponse) contract is redirect-only, with a copy-paste example for gateway authors.</item>
        </change>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>com_alfa</element>
        <type>component</type>
        <version>1.0.9</version>

        <fix>
            <item>Drag-and-drop image upload in the media zone now shows the preview reliably, and gives a clear message when a file is the wrong type or too large — instead of a confusing "no valid files found" error.</item>
            <item>The media upload size limit now follows the server's actual limit, and the standard image types are accepted out of the box when none are explicitly selected.</item>
        </fix>

        <change>
            <item>Reorganised the Media options into clear sections (Storage, Uploads, Thumbnails, Display, Deletion), and merged the two overlapping deletion settings into a single "Complete Media Deletion" option.</item>
            <item>Updated the default media folder and placeholder images.</item>
            <item>Added a "Delete all untracked files" action to Tools → Media for clearing leftover image files that have no database record.</item>
            <item>Added database indexes to the media table for faster media maintenance and listings.</item>
        </change>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>com_alfa</element>
        <type>component</type>
        <version>1.0.8</version>

        <fix>
            <item>The component Options screen now shows "Alfa Commerce: Options" instead of a raw text key.</item>
            <item>Interface text that was previously fixed in English — labels, buttons, headings and messages across the administrator, the storefront and the Cart and Filters modules — is now fully translatable.</item>
            <item>Updated deprecated Joomla document API calls so the storefront stays compatible with current and upcoming Joomla versions.</item>
        </fix>

        <change>
            <item>Tidied the language files: removed duplicate entries and an unused Greek translation, and grouped the strings into clear sections.</item>
            <item>Removed leftover example fields from the component configuration; the currency and subcategory options are now translatable.</item>
            <item>Removed an unused internal model and controller behind the Search Results page.</item>
        </change>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>com_alfa</element>
        <type>component</type>
        <version>1.0.7</version>

        <fix>
            <item>The file-integrity check now refreshes immediately after an update, instead of waiting for its cache to expire.</item>
            <item>Category images now display on the subcategory cards in the product listing.</item>
            <item>The "Payment Methods" and "Shipment Methods" headings on a product no longer appear when there are none to list.</item>
            <item>Clarified the wording of the file-integrity security note.</item>
            <item>Removed the unused Metadata fields from the Place editor (places are not public pages).</item>
        </fix>

        <change>
            <item>The media-zone URL-thumbnail picker now explains that a default image is used if none is chosen, with a tidier preview.</item>
            <item>Categories now use a single image picker (no URL option), matching Manufacturers.</item>
        </change>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>com_alfa</element>
        <type>component</type>
        <version>1.0.6</version>

        <fix>
            <item>Installs without a given language pack are no longer flagged by the file-integrity check.</item>
        </fix>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>com_alfa</element>
        <type>component</type>
        <version>1.0.5</version>

        <addition>
            <item>Multilingual catalog — translate categories, manufacturers, items and more, each in its own language.</item>
            <item>Order statuses with customisable status-change emails for customers and admins.</item>
            <item>Customisable email layouts for order-status notifications.</item>
            <item>Unique values for custom form field options.</item>
            <item>Categories and Manufacturers columns and filters on the Items list.</item>
            <item>Notification centre in the admin — a toolbar bell with a quick panel and a full history.</item>
            <item>File-integrity check (Tools &gt; Security) that verifies your installed files against the official release.</item>
            <item>One-click export of the component as an installable package.</item>
            <item>Automatic updates delivered through Joomla's update manager.</item>
        </addition>

        <fix>
            <item>Custom form field groups now work correctly on a fresh install.</item>
            <item>The database Fix tool (System &gt; Database) now recognises the component.</item>
            <item>Order-status email "Restore defaults" now fills every section, not just the intro.</item>
            <item>Notification sort options now show translated labels instead of raw keys.</item>
            <item>The notification count badge now shows and hides correctly.</item>
            <item>Tools now appears as the last item in the component menu.</item>
        </fix>
    </changelog>
</changelogs>
